<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Yu&#39;s personal website</title>
    <link>https://moonblvd.github.io/brianyao_hugo/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Yu&#39;s personal website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016 Your Name</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/brianyao_hugo/project/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Black Box</title>
      <link>https://moonblvd.github.io/brianyao_hugo/project/smart-black-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moonblvd.github.io/brianyao_hugo/project/smart-black-box/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Variable Autonomy SUAS For NAS Integration</title>
      <link>https://moonblvd.github.io/brianyao_hugo/project/nasa-airplane/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moonblvd.github.io/brianyao_hugo/project/nasa-airplane/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall project goal was to identify and track another small UAS that sporadically flew into andacross  the  field  of  view.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Activity Recognition based on Recurrent Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://moonblvd.github.io/brianyao_hugo/project/lstm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moonblvd.github.io/brianyao_hugo/project/lstm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Human activity recognition uses heterogeneous sensors to capture the state of user and environment. This has wide use in heath-related application such as health monitoring and athlete training. This project proposes a promising human activity recognition approach based on long-short term memory (LSTM) method using the smartphone inertial sensor data. Different kinds of network configuration are tested and explored in our experiment. A comparison with traditional machine learning method is also given in this paper.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RGBD SLAM</title>
      <link>https://moonblvd.github.io/brianyao_hugo/project/rgbd-slam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moonblvd.github.io/brianyao_hugo/project/rgbd-slam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We build a simultaneous localization and mapping (SLAM) system  based on Microsoft Kinect 2 and Robot Operating System (ROS). Our system can estimate the trajectory of a hand held Kinect and generate the point cloud or octomap with color information of the environment. We present our approaches and system architecture in this paper and evaluate its performance through some published datasets as well as data from Kinect. The experiments demonstrate that our system is robust under slow sensor motion and relatively simple environment.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
